https://www.atu.edu/admissions/privacy-policy.php

Skip to main content
Arkansas Tech University
Explore ATU
Explore ATU
This menu contains links to information about the Arkansas Tech University system.
Campuses
This menu contains links to information about each ATU campus.
Future Students
This menu contains links to information relevant to future students.
Current Students
This menu contains links to information for student attending ATU.
Parents & Families
This menu contains links to parent and family information.
Faculty & Staff
This menu contains links to information relevant to faculty and staff.
Alumni & Community
This menu contains links to information for alumni and community members.
Freshman Registration
At Arkansas Tech University (ATU) we want to ensure you have key information to manage
and protect your online privacy.  As such, we have developed this privacy policy to
inform you about what information this website collects, who may receive the information,
and how the information is utilized.
First, ATU does not sell personal information submitted via the ATU website.  Information
collected on the website may either be involuntarily or voluntarily collected.
Involuntary Collection:
Involuntary information that is regularly logged from using our website is utilized
for statistical purposes.  This includes the number of visits and the type of browser.
From time to time, we may use a third-party, session and persistent cookies and similar
technology to collect non-personal information about site usage by our site visitors
to help us remember you and your preferences when you revisit the site.
Additionally, we may allow selected third parties to place cookies through the site
to provide us with better insights into the use of the site, user demographics, or
to provide relevant advertising to you. These third parties may collect information
about a user’s online activities over time and across different websites when he or
she uses our site.
Voluntarily Collection:
A person may also voluntarily provide ATU with personal information via this website
in a case where a user submits an online form.  Online forms are utilized for a variety
of reasons including applying to ATU, requesting information, signing up for services,
etc.  Such information submitted on the site does not contain secure information and
is removed regularly for security purposes.
Accessing Information:
The ATU Office of Information Services incorporates a variety of security features
including encryption and secure logon for pages that a faculty, staff, or student
log into to view personal information.
Additional Warnings:
Some pages of the ATU website include links to external sites. Visitors should be
aware that the privacy policy only pertains to the ATU website, and visitors should
use caution when visiting other sites.
Conclusion:
While we have made every attempt to make this policy clear, please feel free to contact
us if you have additional questions.
Campus Map
215 West O StreetRussellville, Arkansas 72801 USA(844) 804-2628
© 2020 Arkansas Tech University | All Rights ReservedAll trademarks herein belong to their respective owners.Accredited by the Higher Learning CommissionWebsite Accessibility
|
Disclaimer
©
